(Han Seok-kyu)
(Pei Xiancheng)
(Li Rui)
(President Shin Project)
(This drama is purely fictitious. The characters, place names, and institutions that appear in this drama are purely fictional.
Events, groups, occupations, etc. have nothing to do with reality (we hereby inform you)
(Child actors are all accompanied by their guardians
Photographed in a safe environment)
(Review of the previous episode)
The day when Yin Dongxi’s account was credited
something happened
I will wait for you. Please be sure to contact me
Psychiatrist jumps from apartment to death
Then you know that doctor is...
Yoon Dong-hee’s attending physician
Lawyer Cao Bili
Miss Mao Shanmei?
This time…
I really want to help her
Brat, I mean your instincts are right.
Then give it a try and I will help you.
I have something to ask you
Next, you have to check it out.
Let’s see what dangerous things President Shen is doing.
Whenever a sum of money accumulates in Yin Dongxi’s account
Someone will lose their life
Because I'm curious about something
Get out of the way
I have to find him before he's arrested by the police.
Open the door for me, you boy
Xiaojun's father
Before the death of Yoon Dong-hee's attending doctor
The last person to call was the director of the National Forensic Hospital
Dean?
He may be the mastermind behind letting Yoon Dong Hee go.
Or the next target
I think it's one of the two
So which one do you think is more likely?
I'm also curious
So I plan to meet him in person
(12-1, Murin-ro 9-gil, Yongsan-gu, Seoul)
it's me
Found the dean’s address
That...
Can you hear me?
Open the door for me, you boy
Vehicle 6645 is currently entering the northern interchange
(35LA6645)
Right lane ready to merge
Enter interception from behind
A criminal group is located in front of the Northern Toll Gate
Immediate rear support
(35LA6645)
Sir
are you okay
Yoon Dong Hee
(President Shin Project)
(Episode 9)
Sir
Sir, wake up
The patient suffered a stab wound to the abdomen
The bleeding was quite severe and there may have been damage to the retroperitoneum as well.
Hurry up and arrange the operating room. Let’s do a computed tomography scan first.
(Accident and Emergency Department)
Are you a general surgeon?
No, I am a specialist nurse
(operating room)
Dean
Sorry, I didn't catch him
Don't say that. I'm sorry.
The detective blocked the knife for me
We will definitely catch him
But Yoon Dong-hee
How do you know where your home is?
I don't understand how he knew either
Did Yin Dongxi tell you something?
It happened so suddenly...
I have applied for personal safety protection on your behalf
The police are waiting for you outside
thank you
No
How is Detective Choi doing?
He is in the operating room
The process still needs to be observed
Are you Dean Li Xujun?
yes
I want to ask you something
Why did Yin Dongxi want to kill the dean?
And also in public
But…
who are you?
Doesn't look like a police officer
I was 15 years ago...
The person who lost his son because of Yoon Dong Hee
I'm so sorry
Failure to manage prisoners properly
I have to take a lot of responsibility
You and Yin Dongxi
When did you meet?
We don't have a personal relationship
Only some patients
When you feel angry or aggrieved about your situation
will be projected onto the person in charge
their way
May be irrational and bizarre
Even violent
stab someone with a knife
Can you describe it as bizarre?
I mean
Some patients also express emotions in distorted ways
Really?
By the way, I also want to ask you something
Do you know that Yin Dongxi will come to me?
Is that why you appeared there?
No, I went there out of curiosity.
What are you curious about?
Detective Choi told me
The person who last spoke to Yoon Dong-hee’s doctor
Either he's the mastermind behind it, he's the next target.
Can't escape these two
So I want to confirm
Have you checked my call history?
No
Just happened to know
Yoon Dong Hee
Am I the mastermind behind him?
Although this is really unfair to me
But did you get the answer you wanted?
I'm very sorry if any offense was caused.
Ah doctor
The operation was successful
(Operating room) (Family waiting room)
Although the wound is deep
But luckily no internal organs were injured
thank you doctor
Then it shouldn't be life-threatening, right?
yes
are you sure
No money was credited to Yin Dongxi's account today?
Just say no more
What? Did anyone have an accident again?
That bastard Yoon Dong Hee...
Just showed up with a knife.
"The number you dialed is not answered"
"Forwarded to your voice mailbox"
are you okay
Detective Choi
No, don't move yet
The person who last spoke to Yoon Dong-hee’s doctor
Not the mastermind
It's the next target
Am I the mastermind behind him?
Although this is really unfair to me
But did you get the answer you wanted?
(Representative Kim)
Yeah
Brother, I have prepared everything.
I haven't been able to contact you for a while.
He hasn't come to work for a long time
Oh wait for me a moment
"The number you dialed is unavailable"
Even the number has been changed
Did he make up his mind to run away?
Do Dong-seok?
Yes, it seems he changed his phone number.
I want to ask senior if you know his phone number
Don't know
Has his suspension expired?
Suspension?
Lawyer Du Dongxi’s suspension expired in January this year
If it were January…
Then he was hiding the fact that he was suspended.
Also took over the job of legal advisor
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
As an independent and equal business entity
Employees can decide their own working hours
There will be no penalty for absence or tardiness
In fact, the punishment is very severe
Not only do you have to pay a late fee, but class fees will also be deducted.
That's right. What about this part?
Work attire and maintenance of tidy work area
He would ask us to clean like crazy
Dumbbells should be wiped clean one by one
If the mirror gets a little fingerprint on it, it will go crazy
That means you have all been punished, right?
Yes, as long as you are late, you will have to pay an additional late fee.
Then there is evidence
If the employer has clearly designated starting and ending times
If there are also punishment rules
Then prove that the other party regards you as an employee and gives you work instructions.
If you file a lawsuit like this
The court has the opportunity to determine that you are an employee
I originally wanted to use tricks, but I was bitten back on this point.
Not bad
But...how long will this lawsuit take?
Preliminary results will be available in about a year
One year?
We were held back for six months just on salary.
I…
Can't wait that long
I don't have the strength or capital to wait any longer.
Must be established
Is there no other way?
Which article of the law, etc.
So what do you think?
Sister
Why are you here by yourself?
I kept talking about going to Bali all day long and it ended up like this
It’s really been a long time since I drank.
Why does my sister want to go to Bali?
It's so breathless here
I originally thought that after working for a long time, my condition would get better.
I thought that if I just endured it, everything would be fine.
In the end, I found myself being kicked around like a rubber ball.
In the end I left nothing behind
In the end it became I didn’t even know what I really wanted to do
Already forgotten
Yes
until recently
I still feel that what I want to do is not important at all
So…
I will be very grateful to Lawyer Cao
why
because he told me
It is not a matter of course to live a life under the feet of others.
Wait until all the colleagues in the fitness room get their arrears of salary
and after all members’ contracts have been fulfilled
I just want to think carefully
What do you want to do?
Be careful on the road
Do you have an appointment later?
Ah, yes, because I have access control
Walk slowly and thank you for the hospitality
See you next time
I will contact you again
What's wrong?
What are you really doing?
Eat some even if you have no appetite
you lost so much blood
I need to eat something to make up for it.
Hello
I'm so angry that my blood is pouring out now
And I was stabbed in the stomach
Hands are still fine
I will eat it myself
Don't do this kind of thing
Haven’t you found Yoon Dong-hee’s car yet?
Forget it
The team leader said he would never let go of anyone who dared to touch his people.
Now I'm looking for a car myself
Haven't you already adjusted the traffic CCTV?
I didn’t take any photos after passing the big intersection.
I watched it in the central control room for a while
I just came here to help my seniors deliver food.
Why do you need to prepare food for me?
Abominable
Hello
I can eat by myself
You'd better take care of the status of the case.
No
The team leader asked me to stay with you until seniors finish eating.
Stay away from me. I'm very stressed.
Just eat a little, okay?
Xiaojun's father
You go out first
OK
Are you feeling better?
我整个人瞬间清醒了
Watching that guy run away made me angry.
I was injured and felt very embarrassed.
sorry
It's all me irritating you
That's why you got hurt
That's not the case
It is natural for the police to arrest criminals.
thanks to this
Give me a legitimate reason to chase that bastard to the ends of the earth
Detective Choi, I confirmed it
No one sent money to Yin Dongxi this time
How strange
So this time I wasn’t being instigated by anyone.
But he acted on his own?
Detective Choi
October 11 and November 11, 2009
Did something happen?
(Han Jiying died on October 11, 2009)
Zhiying…
(Li Hanzhun died on November 11, 2009)
No alcohol reaction in the blood
No pharmaceutical ingredients were found
Nothing special
He was also present on the day Han Zhiying died.
Li Hanzhun went to eat soup and rice before the accident
Look here
Have you seen this man?
Also…
The day Han Zhiying died
Look here
It's the same man
Who is this person?
Yoon Dong Hee
Do you recognize these people?
I haven't seen it
Both cases ended in accidental death
But it's still an unsolved mystery for me
The same goes for Cha So-yeon’s case.
Are those three people related in any way?
I checked
Cha So-yeon has nothing to do with those two people
but i believe
There must be some secret behind it
(Shen Zaiyi)
(noun Gyeongbuk dialect, shoe seller)
(Example: If a shoe seller comes to our village today
I’ll buy you a pair of shoes)
I'd say you might need to use it longer
So I sent the children away first.
Please feel free to use
Representative Kim
Yes eldest brother
If someone gives you 1 billion
Want you to kill someone
What would you do?
1 billion?
Then that person must be wiped off the face of the earth.
Although I have washed my hands in a golden basin
But if it is 1 billion
I might change my mind
So what do you think about Representative Jin?
A person who usually gets paid to do things
Would you do that kind of thing even if you didn’t get the money?
But who would do a loss-making business?
Frankly speaking
If something happens if you are inexplicably implicated
Isn’t the business over?
encounter that situation
Usually I really want to kill the guy.
Or that person is asking for trouble. There are only two possibilities.
It's definitely for money, right?
Under capitalism, money is everything
Not to mention 1 billion
If it’s 1 billion…
(Sunshine Kindergarten)
(National Forensic Hospital)
Help me retrieve Yin Dongxi’s medical records and visitation records
Can I just call up the most recent record?
Want them all
OK
(resignation letter)
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
President
File a lawsuit?
Didn't you say you won't litigate?
I don't want to file a lawsuit
Who benefits from a lawsuit?
Even if we start the lawsuit now and go through the expedited trial process
It will also take more than a year
So what do you want?
We need to get back the arrears of wages first.
So what method should be used?
Empty the pockets of those who are good at playing legal cards
Now I can finally communicate
Hello
You are here
Why did you come without saying a word?
I have it
and your assistant
this is a gift for you
(courteous reciprocity)
Very handsome
Very handsome, right?
Make me a cup of coffee
Ice, right?
OK
I'm back
Are you back from delivering food?
Yes, you are here
You came just in time
Just right?
What's just right?
Come
On the front is Charlie Hong’s entry time and flight number.
Behind is Do Dongxi’s
Who is Charlie Hong?
Representative of PHG
Do Dong-seok until last year
The salary goes into his wife's account
(Do Dongxi’s transaction list)
But starting from January this year, I transferred it back to my account.
It turns out that I was waiting for the suspension period to end.
Chief Executive Kim, you are really too strong.
Didn't I say it?
This level is nothing to the uncle.
But Master Jin...
Why did you agree to the request of the airborne troops?
What about the promised courtesy?
This is a courtesy exchange, right?
I will collect consent forms from residents for charity bazaar activities
You guys really get along
Du Dongxi not only falsified employee contracts
Even Charliehon was deceived by him
Not only did he violate the Lawyers Law, he was also involved in corruption and malfeasance.
We're going to meet in front of Charlie Hong and Do Dong-seok
Get the evidence
I'll go to the airport and give the evidence to Charlie Hong.
Is it okay for you to go by yourself?
Of course
Leave Du Dongxi to me
To prevent him from ever entering the legal profession again
Shi Wen, aren’t there just a few days left for the diploma exam?
Is it okay to run around like this?
He trampled on the hope of young people working hard to live.
This evil person must be brought to justice
you are so handsome
Shi Wen is a very mature person.
Master Jin: What?
Take a step to speak
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
What's wrong
The link that Yoon Dong-hee received
Can you also pass it on?
Link?
Doesn’t it mean that you will receive a password text message every time you log into your account?
I can do it
But will he watch?
He seems to only confirm certain messages
Send it to me too
with the same code
Let him click on the link and my message will appear
What content do you want to send?
I will take care of this myself
Master Jin, you just need to be responsible for making the links.
(Later entering the business district)
(Fried Chicken Headquarters)
Representative Kim
Now?
I know
where are you going
go meet someone
Representative Kim?
Representative Kim…
They are engaged in construction. They used to be gangsters.
What did he give the president?
Equipment disappeared?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Hey, who could steal such a heavy thing?
I mean it
Could it be that they kept it for themselves and lied to you?
But when I was dealing with No. 1 Store, I was also dealing with them.
而且我也亲自去仓库看过了
Then who will take it?
Those are worth thirty million
Why does your No. 2 store get into trouble all day long?
sorry
Really
What did he give the president?
what key is this
When I went to the gym before
I'm not saying I've seen sports equipment sales lists
There is also a QR Code on it
I only found out after watching it
Representative Kim
Have your employees been exercising lately?
Really, forget it
They'll break the ball when they go bowling.
I went to play baseball and exchanged my bat for reimbursement.
After all, they were all athletes before
It means we are ready
start quickly
Come in quickly
Yes
What are you doing?
Hey, we came to get the equipment but we didn’t see it
Did you sell it to someone else?
What are you talking about? I can't even open the door.
I just asked you to come over and confirm.
Is the person who took away the gym equipment the president?
I was the one who went over first to remove the equipment.
if you don't
will be taken away by antique dealers
money sold
Equivalent to several months’ salary of Mao Shanmei and fellow coaches
This is theft
Wrong
It's because if you leave it alone, that guy Du Dongxi will take it away.
You thought you were asking him to sell the equipment?
Will he use the money to pay back wages?
Airborne Forces. It's up to you.
Is to return the equipment to those scammers
I still have to sell it and give the money from the sale to the staff.
That's right
Anyway, it was the other party who broke the law first
But this is stolen goods
This is the loot
Just sell the equipment
Can we subsidize the salary arrears?
It's not up to me to decide whether to sell it or not.
This is stolen goods
But selling it can make up for the arrears of wages.
This would also break the law for me
I don't care
You thought you were asking him to sell the equipment?
Will he use the money to pay back wages?
Airborne Forces. It's up to you.
Is to return the equipment to those scammers
I still have to sell it and give the money from the sale to the staff.
Is this a store that buys sports equipment?
(Representative Hong Charlie welcomes you back!)
Shi Wen scared me
uncle
why did you come
Because I'm very curious about Charlie Hong's true face
(Representative Hong Charlie welcomes you back!)
The boss who dares to take employees’ salaries to travel abroad
I think he must be very thick-skinned.
You came here because you were worried about me, right?
Not really
In my opinion, you are the least of my worries
Actually I'm a little scared
But with uncle here, I feel relieved
Only when I came to the airport did I realize how big it was.
And there are a lot of people coming and going
Not everyone should take a flight, right?
我们也没有要搭飞机啊
By the way, Schwinn
Let’s take a flight next time
With Ye Yeon
OK
He's coming...
(Representative Hong Charlie welcomes you back!)
Brother Dongxi sent you here, right?
Are you the representative Hong Charlie?
Yes, that's me
I am Charlie Hong
Where are the eyes looking?
but who are you
Is this the water fish that Du Dongxi is talking about?
Water fish? If it’s not a water fish
Is he some kind of boss?
What did you say? No
your legal advisor
Make breaking the law a common occurrence
Misappropriation of public funds, fraud, and malfeasance are all common
Do you know all this?
Are you talking about someone who embezzled public funds, committed malfeasance, or committed fraud?
You are indeed a water fish, right?
Team Leader Li
is representative
Have you brought all the documents?
Of course
Do you want to take this away for free?
What else would I do?
talk to me
So…
What the hell is Dong Seok doing?
Isn’t it all written above?
When not qualified as a lawyer
I signed a contract as a consultant
Put the wages owed to employees into your own pocket
Even holiday bonuses are swallowed up
Also sold second-hand fitness equipment to second-hand dealers
Then they charge a commission in the middle
It's not much money. Why are you making such a fuss...
Oh, you water fish
You will definitely receive a lot later
What kind of complaint about misappropriation of public funds?
Yes
Go to jail for that little money
Then use your body to pay off the debt.
Going to jail?
why should i go in
If you do something wrong, you should be punished.
Didn’t you say you were going to send employees to the Bali branch?
Turns out they're all lying
What happened to the Bali branch?
You lied to employees that you were going to be promoted to Bali branch manager
The result is simply tantalizing.
What you said was too rude, right?
You guy...
No, there is no branch in Bali at all.
Where is the branch manager?
I just heard Du Dongxi say that Bali is very good
That’s why I went there for vacation
Oops…
Look at this stupid water fish
I was severely beaten by Dong Xi.
Then Do Dong-seok…
He bought a 3 billion house in Jiangnan
And in cash
3 billion?
Yeah
Don't you even know that?
This super water fish
Do you know where Do Dongxi is now?
You…
why are you there
are you going to travel
What are you doing? Why are you here?
What else could it be?
Of course, we are here to permanently remove lawyer Do Dongxi.
Talking nonsense about "permanent delisting"
Hello
are you threatening me
You can never catch me legally
Is her name Mao Shanmei?
I also gave her money
I also asked her to sign the receipt, just in case.
I only gave you one month's money, but it was written as if it was all paid in full.
A receipt written in difficult words?
Senior, how about you...
You seem to think you are extremely smart
But where to start?
what do you want to do
Is it against the Lawyers Act?
Or is it a violation of the Labor Standards Act?
Or embezzling public funds behind the boss’s back
Hey what are you doing...
Let's get in the car and talk
I don't want it. Why should I take a ride with a criminal?
where are the criminals criminals
Is this Lawyer Du?
yes that's right
Hello, please walk slowly
Hey, what are you doing?
The barrister wants to kidnap me
Who is it? Who is kidnapping?
Lawyer, do you want to call the police for you?
No, I'm fine
Please walk slowly...
This friend's voice is too loud
why do you do this to me
I said...
Anyway, this thing can't be used as evidence in court.
This is illegally obtained information.
And then what? Embezzlement?
That's what Charlie authorized me to do
You don't understand anything at all
Who said we have to take it to court?
This is usually how it is used
Internal reporting and sowing dissension
humiliating
In short
Make you socially dead
Cao Bili, why on earth are you doing this to me?
You sign here first
Then pay off all the wages owed to employees
Then I'll let you go a little bit
But if you don’t give it...
What if I don’t give it to you?
Jenny Dad
Oh my good daughter
Was it fun in kindergarten today?
Oh, so good
So you are Jenny
Hey super water fish
if it were me
I will definitely chop off that guy's fingers first
Because he will use that hand to steal other people's names
And do all kinds of forgeries
Are you threatening me now?
The premise of the threat is "just in case"
This is informing you
Do you want me to tell you what happens next?
Keep talking. It's so interesting.
Credit card suspension
Account frozen, criminal prosecution
It will also be posted to the chat group of building residents.
The evil deeds of that trash lawyer No. 1103
Children will become famous in kindergarten
My sister-in-law will also become a celebrity in the community
Right
Maybe she will file for divorce
What else are you worried about?
There's nothing to hesitate about, you guy
Why don't you and Dongxi fall into the water and drown?
How about crawling out of there on your own?
If you don't want to be like that, just sign it.
I'll give you three minutes
(three minutes)
no time
two minutes and thirty seconds
Dad I'm sorry for you
I...want to surrender
I surrendered myself
Other teachers have also received funds.
Thank you so much
thank you thank you
so good
Will the store manager and the lawyer be punished?
Penalties for salary arrears are relatively light
The money has been paid and he surrendered again.
So it will be dealt with lightly
Wait
It took a lot of effort to get the money that I was supposed to get.
Plus I lost my job
Why can those people be forgiven so easily?
that's the law
Du Dongxi also saw this clearly.
So I used my brain a little bit
Catch this legal bastard legal villain
it's me
I got your salary back from Du Dongxi.
Really?
thank you
It’s a complete replica of the uncle
You should know it after seeing it
This was all done by Representative Hong
I did everything, you bastard
come out
Hello
You use my 3 billion yuan to buy a house
Do you still want to put all the blame on me?
catch him
Let go please calm down
let me go
come here
You guy, come here
Let me go first
Wait a minute. What is this?
It's nothing, don't do this
What is this? Don’t do this.
Please don't do this. I really don't want this...
Hello
You're a lie from head to toe
Bastard
Hey, I can't stand you anymore
uncle
I'm going to sue this guy for fraud and embezzlement.
In that yellow envelope
There is evidence for my complaint
Evidence?  What evidence do you have?
(complaint)
Why are you writing a complaint?
How could I have written it myself, idiot?
Of course, ask someone smarter than you to write it, idiot.
You cheating bastard
The bastard who brags everywhere
Cao Bili, the bad guy
You are the bad guy
(Plaintiff Hong Fengxiu (stage name: Charlie Hong))
(Defendant Du Dongxi)
Come, take this as evidence
Although I don’t know what it is
But it must have been bought with my money.
This bastard who brags everywhere
Look, he just can't stop bragging.
There are people in the world who love to brag.
Or just do some exercise, you brat.
(The work of treating everyone equally begins now!)
I'll help you when you pull it down
Just hold on as you go up
Do you...do you want to help me?
Shouldn't I do it myself?
take a deep breath
Well done
Four
Because the coach is here
It feels like I'm in a fitness room
I was a little sad because the fitness room was gone.
But exercising outdoors like this actually makes me feel better.
Thank you for trusting me and waiting for me
I just want to thank you
But what are you signing?
Protection of the rights and interests of workers and labor service providers…
If you work but don’t get paid, will you be very angry?
This signature is to prevent this from happening.
For those who are powerless and have no background
When something like this happens to them, they have nowhere to complain.
How much do we have to do to get back as much as we strive to do?
Okay, very good, there must be this method
Come on, let's sign it
Soyeon: I’m pretty awesome, right?
What are you doing? Come here and sign.
There are so many people. Hello everyone.
Boss, you’re here. Hi Shi Wen.
Hello, thank you for your hard work
Is this the Ma Xian City public fitness room that has become very popular recently?
You are here Hello
The last time you experienced a coaching class, you took a quick look at it.
The core seems to be very weak
Who is it me?
Oops, are you talking about him?
How come? It must be talking about you.
How can such an ant's waist be so powerful?
I remember the two of them seemed to be about the same.
what did you say
I'm not married yet
that's what i mean
Why is this guy who is not married yet so weak in waist?
Where did you hit?
I haven't opened this yet. Really?
What are you talking about unopened?
Please go here
Okay, let’s focus on waist exercises today.
You seem to have a knack for making things big.
Let citizens take free coaching classes in public fitness rooms
Helping coaches establish laws to avoid encountering unequal contracts
Isn’t this a win-win situation?
I heard you sold your sports equipment
At the beginning, they said they would only give 30 million
I later sold it for 32 million
Isn't it because some people thought it was stolen goods?
Don't you think it's stolen goods now?
I did it completely legally
I sold it after getting the official transfer documents.
Not the same
It must have been a legitimate threat to get the signature.
How can you say I'm a threat?
This is a negotiation technique for an agreement, okay?
Neither forcing the other party
And I can make decisions in the direction I set
How could the other party find out?
This is not an ordinary skill
But what about advanced techniques?
Am I right? What?
He is a complete replica of his uncle
就连炫耀的样子都一模一样
"It seems you haven't heard my name yet."
"I am Cao Bili"
did he say so
Is there anyone else who hasn't signed?
Some people are called workers, but they are not ordinary workers
Although they work like laborers
but cannot obtain labor rights
For example, freelance workers and platform workers
and specially hired workers
The following is a report by reporter Li Shengen
(Workers who are not ordinary workers... start the road to protect their rights)
came out
Gym instructors who recently encountered unpaid wages
While assisting citizens in fitness
Expanded the scope of labor and labor service providers
Co-signing activities for rights protection
(One of the labor and labor service providers in Ma Xian City
Suggestions on rights protection and assistance terms)
This proposed amendment is aimed at
Freelance workers and platform workers working in Ma Xian City...
Strange, I didn’t do anything
Why do you go to the city hall as a citizen representative?
This is where I’m going to see Representative Quan Fengqin.
Of course I have to be the representative
If it weren't for me
Can Representative Kwon be elected?
Councilor Kwon is the city representative
And I am a citizen representative, understand?
Wow, I wasn't sure yet
Is it really possible to practice law?
I am also a person who does what I say
You're quite handsome. You're also quite photogenic.
What are you talking about?
Go and see if he's waiting down there
What's going on
Zhiyu’s phone keeps turning off
She's never tried this before
Where is the dormitory?
Have you called Jiwoo’s friends to see?
Can't reach her best friend
No one is in the dormitory either
Although it is time to go to school now
But I finished the exam last week
She clearly said she would take a break this week
sorry
I’m contacting you because of something like this. Don’t say that.
well done
Fortunately, Director Pei called me.
How long has Zhiyu’s phone been turned off?
The first time I tried to contact her was five hours ago
We talked on the phone last night before going to bed
I think it just started shutting down this morning.
Have you ever tried this before?
No
Even if I don’t receive a call from time to time…
Zhiyu
what's wrong with you
what happened
Mom, I'm sorry
I forgot to charge my phone
I didn’t know that my phone was turned off.
Kim Ji Woo
Do you know how worried I am?
I went out with Estelle
Estelle's cell phone was also out of battery, so she didn't call you.
You two really are
Mom, I'll call you later. I'm closing the line now.
Sorry, it's okay
Just be fine
what are you doing here
What I do here is none of your business
How can it be okay?
Didn’t you start following me a long time ago?
I'm not following you
You come with me
Let me go, brat
Too noisy here will attract attention
Director Pei
Give him a shot
Injection? What kind of injection?
The needle that shuts you up
He is good at giving injections
Do you want to take a dose of something stronger?
I'm going to kill this guy today
Then go to the police station and surrender
I don't want to see you again either
As soon as I find my stuff I'll be gone
Something?
Guest Sorry
Because I have something urgent
Must close now
What's in this?
If something is installed
what are you going to do
This is my way of making money
Jin Yongyu
That's a doll belonging to your five-year-old daughter. How could you do it?
Zhiyu almost died because of that
is she dead
Not dead?
Didn’t this person save Ji Woo?
I just need to find my stuff
How much is this thing worth?
Large denominations…
Probably three or four
Who gave you that money?
Who gave it...
Who is the person who caught you?
Really amazing
How do you know that's the handle?
No need to say more
As long as I get my stuff back, I'll leave
Do you think that thing is still there?
what
Don't be too ostentatious
Just wait and be content
If you get caught fooling around
I'll cut off your head first and give it to the other party.
Don't even know who the other party is
You dare to threaten me?
Then I will handle it myself and you don't need to worry about it.
Do you want to get an injection before leaving?
Director Pei
Abominable
He can't even handle his own affairs well and is still nosy.
Isn’t this the first time Jin Yongyu has come here?
In fact, he had been here a while ago
Later, because of that person's relationship
I'm worried about Ji Woo
So my nerves are a little tight
thank you
No
Everyone speaks Korean
You really don’t need to tell your mother?
Wait until after the concert is over
I want to give her a surprise
Hurry up and eat spicy fried rice cakes
Then go to the peripheral store
There is also a birthday coffee shop for brothers
Of course
Is that where you can catch the bus?
Well, let’s go
Consent form for market residents
Leave it to me before next week
I'll find a way to get it
There is one more thing
Aren’t we helping each other with something?
Am I on the same level as you?
What's going on
You should stay close to President Shen from now on.
That's what I did
We're doing well now, but we need to do better.
When President Shin is in danger
Be sure to stay close to him
Is it because of Yoon Dong Hee?
How did you know that?
I'm not that slow either
I heard this from my classmates at the police academy.
Also read the case files
The guy who killed Xiaojun escaped
Will the president just sit back and ignore it?
It seems you are smarter than I thought
So reassuring
Otherwise, what did you originally think?
That...
Anyway, just some ideas
(Later entering the business district)
I just need to find my stuff
shut up
Get what Jin Yongyu stole
(No number displayed during call)
How much is this thing worth? Large denomination...
Probably three or four
Whenever a sum of money accumulates in Yin Dongxi’s account
Someone will lose their life
Before the death of Yoon Dong-hee's attending doctor
The last person to call was the director of the National Forensic Hospital
Do you know that Yin Dongxi will come to me?
Is that why you appeared there?
He may be the mastermind behind letting Yoon Dong Hee go.
Or the next target
I think it's one of the two
Just say it’s not me anymore
I really didn’t do it, Mom
Mom…
Why do you prefer...
Why is it the same day?
President, where are you going?
Delivery
where to send
When President Shin is in danger
Be sure to stay close to him
Wait here for ten minutes first
If he doesn't come down, I'll go up.
Considered a strong candidate to be the next Minister of Health and Welfare
Li Xujun, Director of the National Forensic Hospital
expressed the meaning of speech
Regarding the recent escape of inmates
In addition to deeply reflecting on his own responsibilities, he
At the same time, there is also a shortage of medical manpower in the National Forensic Hospital.
made severe criticism
A few days ago I lost a cherished student
(Li Xujun, Director of the National Forensic Hospital)
And she is also an excellent fellow doctor
Although he is responsible for hundreds of treatment and monitoring subjects alone,
Suffering from heavy work and pressure
(Li Xujun, Director of the National Forensic Hospital)
But he never showed any signs of fatigue in front of patients.
Such a hospital working environment
What caused this accident...
You are here
It shouldn't disturb your rest, right?
No way
I was stabbed and didn't die
But these days I feel so bored that I’m going to die.
I'm kidding
you saved my life
I haven't even thanked you properly yet
thank you
don't say that
I heard that you have been investigating Yin Dongxi for a long time?
Yes
me because of that guy
Has it rewritten the history of police punishment?
I heard that you also visited our hospital several times
Yes
Every time I go there, you don't cooperate with the investigation.
I thought you might be here for this
(Medical record sheet)
This is a photocopy of Yoon Dong-hee’s medical records
I can help you
That's all
(Medical Records of Persons Under Monitoring Treatment)
(Name: Yoon Dong-hee)
(Diagnosis and treatment department: Psychiatry Gender/Age: Male/40 years old
Attending physician: Cha So-yeon)
As expected of the dean, he is really capable.
I think I should also rewrite the history of punishment.
Just kidding
I'm very sensitive to the word "punishment"
Not funny at all
It’s the seasoned fried chicken I like. Yours is delicious.
Hey, eat quickly
I like to eat seasoned chicken thighs are delicious
Fried ones are also delicious
Thank you for your hard work. I want to ask the person who delivered the fried chicken.
Where did he go?
Don't know where he went
But he just left not long ago
thank you
You asked me if I knew Yoon Dong-hee, right?
You said you don't know
I carefully checked the records of the prisoners
In the past…
I had a history with him
More than twenty years ago, I was in a juvenile care center
Participated in volunteer service in medical consultation
at that time
I have consulted Yin Dongxi
I didn't hide it from you on purpose
to be honest
He is one of my visitors
Because it didn’t leave a special impression
So I don't remember
Is that so?
And I have confirmed it
You will be there every year on the anniversary of your son’s death
Come meet Yoon Dong Hee
In fact, because this situation is not common
It's convenient for me to ask.
What is your motive?
How can I explain this to you?
Yeah, I guess so
After all, parents who have lost their children
The emotion in my heart is not just pure sadness
There is also a sense of loss
sometimes a sense of guilt and responsibility
intertwined with anger
and went through a complicated mourning process.
You will come repeatedly to meet the perpetrator
It should be one of these emotions
So…
Dean, what do you think?
I think it's for the dead child.
atonement
and for one's own
Comfort?
If you need someone to talk to
Please feel free to contact me
(National Forensic Hospital Li Xujun)
(Money tree, contact me when the money is ready)
Contact me when the money is ready
(Contact me when the money is ready)
(Money tree, contact me when the money is ready)
(Where is the evidence)
He's really crazy
(President Shin Project)
What happened to the president?
I know everything
I want to help too
someone might die
Might also kill people
It depends on how you want to take revenge
It seems that these two people have a close relationship
Maybe it's longer than I thought
Pluto didn't open the door
Go to Anton
you two
Who asked you to come back to Korea casually?
Zhiyu
you want me to...
(If D-7 wants to keep his money, get rid of him)
Kill this man?
It's time for us to end things now